



Profile

Mindful Designer trying to connect people to products. Expertly utilizing graphic design software and learning to bring my ideas to life. A very enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time. Strong interpersonal skills, Social Media Platforms, Photography and Filming.

Enjoy viewing life through multiple perspectives.

Education

National Institute of Design • 2015-2019

BDes in Communication Design. Worked on a variety of projects majoring in a myriad of sub-domains of communication design.

St Mary's Residential School • 2014-2015

High Schooling

Convent of Jesus & Mary

Schooling

Skills

Expertise

Illustrator, Figma, Premier Pro, Photoshop, Adobe XD

Hard Skills

User Research, Wireframing, Design Thinking, Storyboarding, User flows, Research Data Analaysis, Illustrations, Social Media, Photography

Languages

English, Hindi, Malayalam

Experience

Studio 318 • Sept 2020-Dec 2021

Design Strategist & Visualiser

- Designed, facilitated & participated in client workshops & framed insights of user research.
- UI for 318 Website Project Pages
- Desktop and Mobile UI for Shopsy, Flipkart
- · Website UI/UX for SaasBoomi
- Illustrations
- Print digital marketing collaterals

Team Builders India • Jan 2020-Sep 2020

Visual Designer

- Responsible for ideating and execution of many Team Building event graphics and professional communication assets.
- Created online campaigns and digital marketing imagery promotions.

DDB Mudra • Jun 2019- July 2019

Design Intern

- A 2 month summer internship collaborating with Radio FM 94.3. Attended client meetings and conceptualized art based upon brainstorming activities and creative direction.
- Created Concept Sketches & Deliverables

Freelance

- Designed and developed the collaterals (tshirts, id cards, notebooks, bags) & website for a pre primary school Mahara- both Mobile and Desktop. Created concept sketches, User flows, wireframes and Style guide.
- Logo Designing for a Jewellery Brand Vega Sree.
- Logo Designing, Photography and Social Media Templates for a clothing brand Anokha. Also designed the tshirts.